{
    "id": "16b0c20ddc714422924cab4abee66e2c",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ................... a discussion with my boss in the morning.",
            "description": "In the morning usually refers to past time hence, the simple past is preferred with it. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "have had"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They ...................... to our proposal.",
            "description": "The present perfect is commonly used to announce news.",
            "answers": [
                "agreed",
                "have agreed",
                "had agreed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody knows how he .................... from the prison.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "escape",
                "has escaped",
                "escaped"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The ship has ……………………………….",
            "description": "People drown ships sink.",
            "answers": [
                "sank",
                "sunk",
                "drown",
                "drowned"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "When I talked to her I realized that she ....................... depressed",
            "description": "When the main verb is in the past tense, we usually use past tenses in the subordinate clauses as well. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "is",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... to him since our last meeting.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used to talk about time up to now. ",
            "answers": [
                "didn't talk",
                "haven't talked",
                "hadn't talked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................... out every day.",
            "description": "The simple present is used to talk about habits, routines etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "am working",
                "work",
                "have worked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither the manager nor his secretary ...................... present in the office.",
            "description": "When we connect two singular subjects with neither/nor, the verb is singular. ",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The quality of life in urban areas ......................... deteriorating.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun quality. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "have been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Even the mightiest .................... prey to death.",
            "description": "The mightiest is a plural expression.",
            "answers": [
                "fell",
                "has fallen",
                "have fallen"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................... here a moment ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "is"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She .................... yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not return",
                "has not returned",
                "do not return"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}